#### **Mohammad Nauman Bhat**

Email: Nomi.rashid26@gmail.com

Phone: +91 9596353460





## About me!

Myself Mohammad Nauman Bhat and I am from One Way Bilal Abad Khrew Pampore 191103, Jammu and Kashmir India and I am a developer so I develop apps for Windows, android and other platforms and I am also a Microsoft Student Partner for last 2 years I have also many interests like dancing, singing, playing etc. I like coding, programming and developing I have created so many apps like Universal HD Player for Windows. I love to join coding contests like Google Code-in and Google Summer of Code and much more. I have received a certificate from Google-Code-in program last year and I am also a full stack developer.



# **Experience**

#### **Microsoft Student Partner**

Aug 2017 - Present

#### Microsoft

The Microsoft Student Partners is a worldwide recognizable program to sponsor students majoring in disciplines related to technology. The MSP program enhances students' employability by offering training in skills not usually taught in academia, including knowledge of Microsoft technologies.

#### In 2017!

I received a Microsoft Student Partner Certificate.

#### Now in 2018!

I created a Windows App for Microsoft called "Universal HD player".



#### **Firefox Student Ambassador**

Sept 2017 - Present

#### Mozilla

I joined Mozilla in 2017 and Mozilla is an open source organisation which believes in openness, being open source. Mozilla loves its people (FSA's) who helps community in creating awareness about Mozilla and its mission.



### Google Code-in

#### Google

I joined Google Code-in contest in 2017 I solve lot of tasks and I received a certificate from Google Code-in and a t-shirt.



## **Education**

Green Valley 2016 – Present

B. Tech in Computer Science



### **Light House Public School Khrew**

2000 - 2015

I studied nursery to 12th standard in this institute



## **Skills**

C# • Windows Phone App Development • Windows 8 App development • HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3 • C++



# **Certifications**

- MSP Certificate Microsoft
  - Dec 2017
- Hour of Code www.code.org
  - Nov 2017
- National Human Rights Certificate Government
  - June 2018
- Google Code-in Certificate
  Google
  - Dec 2017
- Khelo India Certificate Government
  - March 2018

# **Joining Letter**

- 📵 Internshala
  - ISP 9.0 Joining letter
  - 2017